okay so we're back again and we're gonna
好，所以我们又回来了，我们要
talk a little bit about what's known as
谈论一些所谓的
the Meyerson Satterthwaite theorem so
Meyerson Satterthwaite定理是
mark Satterthwaite you've seen his name
马克·萨特思韦特，你已经看过他的名字
on several different theorems now the
现在根据几个不同的定理
muler Satterthwaite Gibbard
穆勒Satterthwaite Gibbard
Satterthwaite and now the Meyerson
Satterthwaite，现在是Meyerson
Satterthwaite theorem and what this
Satterthwaite定理和这是什么
theorem refers to is trade and it's
定理是指贸易，它是
basically going to say that it's going
基本上会说它将
to be difficult to get efficient trade
很难获得有效的贸易
out with voluntary participation and
自愿参加
when we talked about strikes and so
当我们谈论罢工等
forth at the beginning of last week one
上周初四
thing that's going to be important in
重要的事情
understanding why we might have
了解我们为什么会有
difficulties in getting trade out is
取得交易的困难是
that people could have private
人们可以有私人的
information about their utilities for
有关其实用程序的信息
various exchange of goods so how much am
各种商品交换多少钱
I really willing to work how much to do
我真的很愿意工作多少
do I value a particular job can we
我看重某项工作吗？
design a mechanism that always results
设计一种始终可以实现的机制
in efficient trade our strikes
在高效贸易中，我们的罢工
unavoidable that's the basic essence
不可避免的是基本要素
here and the conclusions that we're
这里和我们得出的结论
going to find out of this result are
要找出这个结果是
going to be that if it's not always
如果不是总是这样的话
completely obvious that a trade should
完全显而易见，交易应该
be taking place then it's going to be
会发生，那将会是
impossible to align incentives to get
无法调整激励措施以获得
efficient trade out even just an amazing
高效的交易，甚至只是一个惊人的
incentive compatible way and so we don't
激励兼容的方式，所以我们不
look at the very very simple trade
看看非常非常简单的交易
setting and even in that simple trade
设置，甚至在那种简单的交易中
setting we're going to see that there's
设置，我们将看到
going to be difficulties in getting
很难获得
efficient trade out and that is is
有效的交易，那就是
really a very important and fundamental
真的非常重要和根本
result that comes out of game theory and
博弈论得出的结果
mechanism design in terms of
机制设计方面
understanding why it is that we're going
了解为什么我们要去
to have breakdown in bargaining why it
讨价还价的原因
is that we don't always get efficient
是我们并不总是有效率
outcomes this is really a you know
结果，这真的是你知道的
fundamental insight and that came out of
基本洞察力
this area okay so this it'll be a fairly
这个区域好，所以这将是一个相当
easy one to see to so we're gonna look
容易看到的，所以我们要看
at an exchange of a simple a single unit
交换一个简单的单个单元
of an indivisible good okay so just I've
不可分割的好吧，所以我
got I've got something I've got a car I
我有东西我有车我
want to sell it and I know how much it's
想卖掉它，我知道多少钱
worth to me you know how much it's worth
对我来说值得，你知道它有多少价值
to you and we start haggling okay so
给你，我们开始讨价还价，所以
we're going to haggle over this and in
我们将对此进行讨价还价
particular let's think of the seller the
特别让我们想到卖方
seller has some value
卖方有一些价值
in zero one so we're just going to
在零，所以我们只是要
normalize things to lie in the unit
使事物归于单位
interval but think of this as say that
间隔，但认为这是说
the sellers value for this car they're
卖家对这辆车的价值
not going to give it away from nothing
不会放弃一切
they have some value for how much is it
他们有多少价值
really worth before they're going to be
在他们成为之前真的很有价值
willing to part but the buyer shows up
愿意分手，但买家出现
the buyer has some value for the car as
买方对汽车有一些价值，因为
well
好
theta B and generally we're going to
theta B，通常我们要
think of this as you know sometimes the
想到这一点，你知道有时
buyer is going to have a higher value
买家将拥有更高的价值
than the seller sometimes they might not
比卖方有时他们可能不
sometimes the buyer might think that the
有时买家可能会认为
car's not worth as much as the seller
汽车的价值不如卖方
thinks it's worth and therefore that it
认为这是值得的，因此
won't be efficient to trade and so we're
交易效率不高，所以我们
in a setting where we've got these two
在我们拥有这两个的环境中
different valuations and now they start
不同的估值，现在他们开始
going through some mechanism haggling
通过一些机制讨价还价
and we want to see what the outcome
我们想看看结果如何
looks like okay let's do a very simple
看起来不错，让我们做一个非常简单的事情
example which will be useful in
这个例子将在
illustrating and actually proving the
说明并实际证明
main theorem here so let's think of a
这里的主要定理，让我们考虑一个
situation where the buyers value can
买方价值可以达到的情况
either be very low point one or high at
要么是低点一，要么是高点
one and the seller can either think that
一个，卖方可以认为
this thing's worthless
这东西一文不值
a value of zero or they're really
零值或它们实际上是
attached to it at point nine okay so
在第九点附加到它，所以
we've got these two values for the buyer
我们为买家提供了这两个值
and two values for the seller and what's
卖方的两个值是什么
true is if we look at different
诚然，如果我们看不同
combinations they could have basically
他们基本上可以有的组合
in all cases except one the buyer's
在所有情况下，除了一个买方的
value is higher than the sellers value
价值高于卖方价值
so in three out of the four cases that
所以在四种情况中的三种
are possible these combinations the so
这些组合是否可能
you know we can think of listing buyers
你知道我们可以想到上市买家
value first then sellers value you could
首先重视，然后卖方重视
have 0.1 zero
有0.1零
we could have 0.1 0.9 we could have 1 0
我们可以有0.1 0.9我们可以有1 0
or 1.9 so those are the four
或1.9，那是四个
combinations and basically in three of
组合，基本上是三个
these the buyers value is higher than
这些买家的价值高于
the sellers and we should have a
卖方，我们应该有一个
transaction because now there's an
交易，因为现在有一个
efficiency gain in trading the good from
货物交易效率的提高
the seller to the buyer we get a higher
卖方对买方，我们得到更高
utility they can make a payment
他们可以付款的实用程序
there's gains from trade here okay the
这里的贸易有好处
only case where there shouldn't be trade
只有在不应该交易的情况下
is this case where the buyer ends up
在这种情况下，买方最终
having a lower value thinks it's not
较低的值认为不是
very worth very much
非常值得
seller thinks it's worth a lot in that
卖家认为这很值得
case it's better to leave it in the
最好把它留在
sellers hands it's more valuable to the
卖家之手，这对
seller than the buyer okay that's the
卖方比买方好，那就是
setting and let's think of a mechanism
设置，让我们想到一种机制
here so let's suppose that the seller
在这里，让我们假设卖方
gets to name any price okay so this is a
可以说出任何价格了，所以这是一个
simple take-it-or-leave-it offer so the
简单的“接受”或“离开”提议，因此
seller just puts out a price and says
卖方只是拿出一个价格说
here's my advertised price I'm not gonna
这是我标价的价格
listen to anything you either say yes or
听任何您说是或
no at this price okay and the buyer
不可以这个价格，买家
either buys or not at that price so
要么以该价格购买，要么不以该价格购买
let's think of this world and in this
让我们想起这个世界
case let's think of the seller basically
案例让我们基本上想到卖家
should either sell at a price of 0.1 or
应该以0.1的价格出售，或者
or one I mean selling at a price of 0.5
或一个我的意思是以0.5的价格卖出
doesn't make sense if you're the seller
如果你是卖方，那没有任何意义
you could still charge point 6 and the
您仍然可以充电第6点，
high value buyer would still want to buy
高价值买家仍想购买
it at point 6 rather than 1.5 and the
它在第6点而不是1.5，并且
low value buyer isn't going to want to
低价值的买家不会想要
buy it either of those so once you go
买那些，所以一旦你去
above point 1 you might as well push the
在第1点以上，您最好按一下
price all the way up to 1 and you don't
价格一直上涨到1，而您却没有
want to sit down near 0 you might as
想坐在0附近，你可能会
well push it all the way up to point 1
一直将其推至第1点
okay so we'll presume that the buyer
好吧，我们假设买家
says yes 1 indifferent but modulo some
说是1漠不关心但取模一些
Epsilon
厄普西隆
basically that the seller should be
基本上，卖方应该
saying a price that either pushes up to
说一个价格，要么推高
the point 1 or all the way up to 1 okay
点1或一直到1好
and now when we think about the seller
现在，当我们考虑卖方时
so imagine that the seller actually
试想一下，卖方实际上
thinks the car is worthless but they're
认为汽车毫无价值，但他们
the only one who knows that and the
唯一知道这一点的人
buyers going to show up and now the
买家将出现，现在
seller can post a price and if I post a
卖家可以发布价格，如果我发布
price of 0.1 that's a sale for sure
0.1的价格肯定是一笔销售
expected utility point 1 okay so I
预期效用点1好，所以我
charged a low price I'm gonna sell to
收取了我要卖给的低价
both buyers price of 1 I sell at the
我的两个买方价格都以
high price what happens now if the
高昂的价格，如果现在
buyers types are equally likely I'm
买家类型也很可能
gonna sell only to the high type and my
只会卖给高级客户
expected utility is I'm gonna sell at a
预期的效用是我要在
value of 1 when the value is high so the
值1时该值较高，因此
the sellers value from a transaction in
卖方在以下交易中的价值
this case is going to be plus P and then
这种情况将是加P，然后
minus the value of the seller which is 0
减去卖方的价值0
so they don't give any they don't lose
所以他们不给任何他们不输的东西
anything by giving it away to get plus P
付出任何就可以得到加P
so in this case they're getting a price
所以在这种情况下，他们要价
of 1 probability 1/2
1的概率1/2
utility of 1/2 okay so what's true here
1/2的效用，那么这里是什么
is if you allowed this hour to make it
是如果你允许这个小时
take it or leave it offer they should
接受它或留下它，他们应该
set the price at a high enough level
将价格定在足够高的水平
that you're only going to get trade to
你只会去交易
the high type and so now what we end up
高类型，所以现在我们结束了
with is an inefficiency right so even
与是低效率的权利，所以即使
though the sellers value is zero when
尽管当
the buyers value is 0.1 we're not
买家价值是0.1我们不是
getting a trade okay that's so there's
得到一个好的交易，所以有
where the inefficiencies sometimes the
有时效率低下的地方
buyer has a higher value than the seller
买方的价值高于卖方
and we're not getting trade okay so
而且我们的交易还不好，所以
that's the basic inefficiency so we're
这是基本的低效率，所以我们
better off to set the high price in
更好地设定高价
terms of the seller and we get an
卖方的条款，我们得到
inefficient trade these don't trade even
低效的交易，这些甚至不交易
though they should okay what about other
虽然他们应该没事其他
mechanisms well let's suppose that we
机制，让我们假设我们
sort of forced the seller to somehow
某种程度上迫使卖方以某种方式
charge a lower price or the the that's
收取较低的价格或
you know the the buyer said okay I you
你知道买家说好吧你
know after the fact in that the seller
知道事实之后，卖方
sets this high price of 1 the buyer
设置此高价1买方
comes back and says you know really it's
回来说你知道这是真的
too bad I was the low value buyer you
太可惜我是低价买家
really should have sold it to me I was
我真的应该把它卖给我
willing to pay point 1 you still walk
愿意支付您仍然走的第1点
away with something from for this if
远离一些东西，如果
they're so actually sells when you tell
当你告诉他们时，它们实际上是在卖
them that story then the high value
他们那个故事那么高价值
buyer might as well tell that story
买家不妨讲这个故事
right so the high value buyer is going
对，所以高价值的买家要去
to want to pretend to be the low value
要假装为低价值
buyer and drive the price down to point
买方并压低价格
1 so the basic difficulty in getting
1所以获得的基本困难
this is if you're willing to sell at the
这是如果您愿意在
low price to the low buyer the high
低价向低价买家高价
price buyer can try and pretend to be
价格买方可以尝试假装
the low priced buyer and so the
低价买家，所以
incentive compatibility condition is
激励相容条件为
going to mean it's going to be very
意味着这将是非常
difficult to get efficient trade always
总是很难获得有效的贸易
be getting the good to be sold when it
当它被出售时得到商品
when you want it to and not have people
当你想要它而没有人时
try to pretend to be somebody else so
试着假装别人
the mechanism is not going to work if we
如果我们不这样做，该机制将无法正常工作
actually want to get efficient trade out
其实想得到有效的交易
okay so what does the theorem say it
好，那定理怎么说
says that there exists distributions on
说存在分布
the buyers and sellers valuations such
买卖双方的估价
that there is not exist any mechanism
没有任何机制
any mechanism which is going to be
任何将要成为机制的机制
Bayesian instead of compatible which is
贝叶斯而不是兼容
efficient weekly budget balance
每周有效预算余额
and interim individual irrational so if
和临时的个人非理性，所以如果
you want to make the decision of in this
您想在此做出决定
case trading always when you should and
总是在需要的时候进行案例交易
not trading when you shouldn't making
不应该交易时不进行交易
sure that it's weekly budget balance so
确保这是每周预算余额
that the amount that the buyer pays is
买方支付的金额为
at least the amount that the seller gets
至少卖方获得的金额
so we're not having to stick in extra
所以我们不必坚持
money in order to make this thing work
为了使这个东西起作用而要花钱
and its interim individual irrational so
及其临时的个人非理性
individuals don't want to walk away once
个人不想一次走开
they're told their value and told what
他们被告知自己的价值，并告诉他们什么
what they expect to get out of this
他们期望从中得到什么
mechanism they don't want to walk away
他们不想走开的机制
from the mechanism okay so that's the
从机制还可以，那就是
theorem and before we go into the proof
定理和我们进入证明之前
let me say a little bit about why the
让我说说为什么
this first part says there exists
第一部分说存在
distributions for which this is true you
您认为这是正确的分布
there are some situations where you
在某些情况下，您
could get efficient trade okay and let
可以进行有效的交易，让
me just go through one to make clear
我只是通过一个明确
what's going on here suppose that we
这是怎么回事，假设我们
were in situation where the buyers value
处于买家重视的情况
is always above some value of e and the
总是高于e的某个值，并且
sellers value is always below that okay
卖家的价值总是低于那个还可以
so there's some level V and we know that
所以有一些V级，我们知道
buyers always value these cars more and
买家总是更看重这些车，
sellers always value the cars less well
卖家总是不太看好汽车
indexed with that world there's a simple
索引到那个世界，有一个简单的
mechanism always exchange the good and
机制总是交换善良和
it always exchange it at a price of fee
它总是以收费的价格交换它
okay so the the buyer pays V the seller
好的，所以买方向卖方支付V
gets V that's going to be strategy proof
获得V，这将是战略证明
it's going to be individually rational
这将是个人理性的
it's going to satisfy budget balance the
它会满足预算平衡
the payments add up to zero so that's a
付款加起来为零，所以
setting where we get all the conditions
设定我们得到所有条件的地方
we want and it's because we know that
我们想要，这是因为我们知道
there always should be trade and we know
总应该有贸易，我们知道
that there's a price that is always
总有一个价格
going to please that all the buyers and
要取悦所有买家和
all of the sellers okay so it's not
所有的卖家都可以，所以不是
going to be that this theorem is true
这定理是正确的
regardless of what distribution is it's
不管是什么分布
going to have to be that these
必须是这些
distributions cross over and that
分布交叉，那
sometimes we want trade and sometimes we
有时我们想要贸易，有时我们
don't and we've looked at an example
不，我们看了一个例子
like that and in fact let's show the
这样，实际上让我们展示
proof based on our example so buyers
证明基于我们的例子，所以买家
values are equally likely to be 0.1 or
值很可能是0.1或
one sellers values are equally likely to
一个卖家的价值同样有可能
be zero or
为零或
point-9 trade should take place for all
第9点贸易应为所有人
combinations of values except point 1.9
点1.9以外的值的组合
in terms of efficient trade and so what
在有效贸易方面，又如何
we can do is just go through the
我们可以做的就是
conditions try to satisfy them and show
条件试图满足他们并显示
that we can't satisfy them in in all the
我们无法在所有方面满足他们
situations what I'm going to do is I'm
情况下我要做的是
going to show the proof for full budget
将显示完整预算的证明
balance not weak budget balance so
预算余额不弱，因此
that's gonna make the proof a little bit
那会证明一点点
easier it's gonna be very easy to extend
更容易扩展
so I will allow you to do that to the
因此，我将允许您对
case where we don't require full budget
我们不需要全部预算的情况
balance and so here what we're going to
平衡，这就是我们要做的
have is trade should take place for all
所有人都应该进行贸易
the combinations except when the buyer
组合，除非买方
and seller values are point one and
卖方的价值是第一点
point nine and that the nice part about
第九点，关于
that just in terms of notation is that
就符号而言，就是
means that we can write payments down in
意味着我们可以将付款记入
terms of our full budget balance just as
与我们的全部预算余额一样
a single price which is this as the
单个价格是
payment made by the buyer and received
买方付款并收到的付款
by the seller so we can think of some
由卖方，所以我们可以想到一些
price as a function of what the buyer
价格是买方的函数
and sellers value is this is the price
卖家的价值就是这就是价格
paid from the buyer to the seller okay
从买方向买方向卖方付款
and week budget balance the thing is now
和周预算平衡的事情现在
you're gonna have two prices one paid by
您将获得两个价格，其中一个由支付
the buyer or the other received by the
买方或
seller and the payment paid by the buyer
卖方和买方支付的款项
is always gonna have to be at least the
总是至少要
the payment received by the seller and
卖方收到的付款和
you'll see we're quite easily that
你会看到我们很容易
that'll bound these things so the thing
这将约束这些东西
we say Anna proof will work through for
我们说安娜证明将通过
that case okay so first thing what has
这样的话好吧，第一件事是
to be true if in the situation where the
在以下情况下为真
values are one in point nine so the the
值是第九点之一，因此
seller has a value of 0.9 buyer has a
卖方的值为0.9买方的值为
value of one by the individual
一个人的价值
rationality of the seller and here we're
卖方的合理性，我们在这里
using ex-post individual rationality in
在事后运用个人理性
this part of the proof its 0.9 and again
这部分证明是0.9
I'm gonna leave it to you to extend this
我会留给你扩展
to an expected value of the interim
到中期的期望值
individual rationality condition here
这里的个人理性条件
I'll do the ex post version again the
我将再次发布后期版本
extension is fairly straightforward
扩展相当简单
you'll just be working with expected
您将按预期工作
payments instead of actual payments so
付款而不是实际付款，因此
here the payment conditional on high
这里的付款条件是高
valued buyer and high valued sellers at
尊贵的买家和高价卖家
point-9 otherwise the seller doesn't
第9点，否则卖方不会
want to sell it when we see a low valued
当我们看到低价时想卖掉它
buyer and a low valued seller than the
买家和低价卖家
price can't be more than point one
价格不能超过第一点
otherwise the buyer won't want to buy it
否则买家将不愿购买
so individuality means the price in that
所以个性意味着价格
case has to be at the low point one when
情况必须在最低点
we don't have trade so when there's no
我们没有交易，所以当没有
trade the price exchange is going to
交易价格交换去
have to be zero and that's going to have
必须为零，这将不得不
to be true because of the individual
因为个人而真实
rationality constraints of both the
两者的理性约束
buyer and a seller the buyer is not
买方和卖方不是买方
getting anything so it can't be more
得到任何东西，所以它不能再更多了
than zero and the sellers not giving
大于零，卖家不给
anything away so they can't be charged
一切都走了，所以他们不能收费
anything either so the the price is
任何东西，所以价格是
going to have to be zero in a case where
在以下情况下必须为零
we have no trade and so now we've got
我们没有交易，所以现在我们有了
three conditions on three of the prices
价格的三个条件
and what we want to do is fill in the
而我们要做的是填写
fourth price okay so now what we need to
第四价格好，所以现在我们需要
do is we've got individuation how are
我们要做的是个性化
you satisfied for three of the prices we
您对我们的三个价格感到满意
want to make sure we're going to give an
想要确保我们要给
individual rationality here well that's
这里的个人理性是
going to be easy any price between zero
零之间的任何价格都将变得容易
and one will be individually rational
一个人将是个人理性的
the difficulty is going to be to get the
困难将是获得
incentive compatibility condition to
激励相容条件
hold okay so now we want to check what's
保持良好，所以现在我们要检查什么
going to be true so that that people
是真实的，以便那个人
want to tell us what their actual values
想告诉我们他们的实际价值
are okay so instead of compatibility for
可以，所以与其兼容
the seller of type zero not wanting to
类型为零的卖方不想
pretend to be 0.9 type let's go through
假装为0.9类型，让我们来看一下
that if I actually truthfully say that
如果我真的如实地说
I'm a type zero what am I going to get
我是零类型我会得到什么
well half the time I'm going to be faced
一半的时间我要面对
with a buyer of type one half the time
与一半类型的买家一起
I'm faced with a buyer of type point one
我遇到一个第一类的买家
so my expected utility is going to be a
所以我期望的实用程序将是
bridge of those two prices and it has to
这两个价格的桥梁，它必须
be better than me pretending that I'm a
比我假装自己更好
point nine type so alternatively I could
点九型，所以我可以
pretend that I'm a point nine type
假装我是九点型
instead and these would be the prices I
相反，这些将是我的价格
would get okay so in that situation we
会好起来的，所以在那种情况下，我们
can ask and I have a no value for the
可以问，我没有任何价值
good so it doesn't really matter in
很好，所以在里面并不重要
terms of what where the good goes so in
善举何以如此
this case this turns out to be the
这种情况原来是
incentive compatibility condition let's
激励相容条件让我们
check what that implies so
检查这意味着什么
by one two and three we have bounds on
一二三
how low this price can be how high this
这个价格可以低到多少
price can be and we know exactly what
价格可以，我们确切知道
this price is so we know that this one
这个价格是，所以我们知道这一个
this last one has to be zero we know
我们知道这最后一个必须为零
that this one is the point one point
那一点就是一点
nine is at least point nine and this one
九至少是点九，而这一点
is at most point one and so in terms of
最多是第一点，因此
an inequality we know that this over all
不平等，我们知道这一切
and multiplying through by the two p10
然后乘以两个p10
plus point one has to be greater than
加点必须大于
equal to 0.9 points plus zero okay so we
等于0.9点加零好，所以我们
can take what we know from one two and
可以从一二中得到我们所知道的
three plug them in here on in terms of
三个将它们插入此处
bounds given that we have the inequality
假设我们有不等式
pointing from the left to the right and
从左到右指向
that tells us then that p10 has to be at
然后告诉我们p10必须位于
least point eight okay so in order to
至少要点八点好，这样才能
make sure that the seller doesn't want
确保卖方不想要
to pretend they have the high value when
假装他们有很高的价值
they really have the low value the price
他们真的很便宜
is gonna have to be at least point eight
至少要到八点
when they have the low value and the
当它们的价值低而
other the buyer has the high value okay
其他买家有高价好吗
do the same incentive compatibility with
与...做相同的激励兼容性
the buyer being a high value not wanting
买家是高价值的，不想要
to pretend that they have a low value
假装他们的价值很低
not trying to drive the price down and
不试图压低价格，
basically this is going to be a reverse
基本上这将是相反的
kind of calculation of the same thing
对同一事物的某种计算
and given all the symmetry here it's not
考虑到这里所有的对称性
going to be surprising you can work
你可以工作会很惊讶
through the details do exactly the same
通过细节做完全一样
kind of calculation and what do you end
怎样的计算，你要结束什么
up with one two and three now we're
现在一二三
going to imply that this price has a cap
暗示这个价格有上限
of point two okay so the seller has to
第二点还可以，因此卖方必须
be getting at least a price of 0.8 the
至少获得0.8的价格
buyer can't be seeing a price of more
买家看不到更高的价格
than point two well it's going to be
比第二点好
difficult to find a price which is at
很难找到一个价格
least point eight and also no more than
最少八点
point two at the same time that's
同时指出两个
impossible so that's the end of the
不可能，所以这就是结束
proof basically once we put in the
基本上，一旦我们放入
individual rationality conditions then
那么个人的合理性条件
the incentive compatibility conditions
激励相容条件
are going to say the price has to be
要说的是价格必须是
pretty high to keep the seller honest
很高，可以保证卖方诚实
and the price gonna have to be very low
价格必须非常低
to keep the buyer honest can't do that
保持买家诚实不能这样做
at the same time no price is going to
同时没有价格
work so incentive competitive
工作，激励竞争
puts individuality plus having trade
注重个性加上贸易
exactly in the right situations is going
恰恰在正确的情况下
to be impossible so in terms of summary
不可能，所以就总结而言
what have we learned
我们学到了什么
private information about values
有关价值的私人信息
necessitates some inefficiencies and
导致效率低下，
voluntary trade and at least two sort of
自愿贸易和至少两种
basic tension between incentives and
激励措施与
efficiency and and and this is really
效率，而这确实是
impossible to get around and one thing
不可能到处走一件事
to emphasize here and this is sort of
在这里强调，这有点
the power of the revelation theorem
启示定理的力量
think of any mechanism you you would
想想你会采用的任何机制
want right think of any mechanism if
想正确地考虑任何机制，如果
that mechanism somehow has equilibrium
该机制某种程度上具有平衡
that leads to efficient trade we can
导致有效的贸易，我们可以
write that mechanism as a direct
将该机制写为直接机制
mechanism and so the proof here says no
机制，所以这里的证明说不
matter what's going on you know
不管发生了什么，你知道
throughout this mechanism it's going to
在整个机制中，
be impossible to write anything down
不可能写下任何东西
that's gonna have the desired properties
这将具有所需的属性
of always trading when you want to and
在需要时总是进行交易
being instead of compatible people are
而不是兼容的人是
gonna tend to lie and that's gonna lead
会撒谎，这会导致
to some inefficient trades and and not
一些低效率的交易，而不是
having things not happen when you want
当你想要的时候事情不会发生
them to and you know this begins to
他们去，你知道这开始
explain this question of why do we have
解释为什么我们有这个问题
strikes you know why do we have
罢工你知道我们为什么有
breakdowns
细目
why don't we always come to an agreement
为什么我们不总是达成协议
and you can ask yourself you know if you
你可以问问自己你是否知道
ever walked away from a bargain when you
曾经从讨价还价中走出来
thought that a trade might really be
以为交易可能真的是
possible so sometimes we're going to be
可能，所以有时我们会
forced to leave things on the table and
被迫把东西放在桌子上，
that's that's a powerful result and
那是一个有力的结果，
understanding this is really important
了解这一点非常重要
and sort of understanding why some
并理解为什么有些
inefficiency exists in the world and why
世界上存在效率低下的原因
we're going to have difficulties getting
我们将很难获得
around them to the extent that people
在人们周围
have private information about their
有关于他们的私人信息
willingness to do something that's going
愿意做某事
to be difficult to overcome in in
难以克服
getting full efficiency
获得充分的效率